嘿
Hey.
不会有事的
It's going to be okay.
只要告诉我 我们做的是正确的事
Just tell me we're doing the right thing.
不 亲爱的 我知道 你想去修补
No, sweetheart,I know you want to fix this.
这是你的本行 但我们尽力了
It's what you do.But we've tried.
好吗？我们尽力了 但看看结果是什么
All right? We've been trying and look where it's gotten us.
我觉得 分开一段时间对他有好处
And I think the space is gonna be good for him.
对我们都好 而且 这是一所好学校
For all of us.Besides, it's a good school.
等夏天一过 他就回家了
He'll be home by the end of the summer.
是啊
Yeah.
我不会有事的 我保证
I'll be okay.I promise.
我保证
I promise.
我爱你
Love you.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
- 打电话给我  - 我会的
- Call me.  - Will do.
我爱你
I love you.
哇
Wow.
好棒 史蒂芬
Well done, Stephen.
太棒了！
Amazing!
住手，妈妈！
Oh, stop, Mom!
- 那是什么？那是什么？ - 什么？ 噢
- What's that? What's that?  - Huh? Oh!
一，二，三！
One, two, three!
- 漂亮  - 耶！
- Nice.  - Yeah!
它基本上死了
He's pretty dead.
它死了
He's very dead.
今天 我儿子成了大人
Today my son has become a man.
为此...
Because of that...
我知道 你觉得 我们这么做是为了惩罚你
I know you think we're probably doing this to punish you
但我们不是
but we're not.
好吗？
All right?
你妈妈和我 是为了你好
Your mother and I want the best for you.
你根本不知道 她想要什么
You have no idea what she wants.
我不知道 你为什么这么做
I don't know why you're doing this.
是你被学校开除的
I'm not the one that got expelled, pal.
她不想赶我走 是你想
Well, she doesn't want me gone. It's you.
不是的，史蒂芬
That's not true,Stephen.
就是的，你要把我送走
Yes, it is.You're sending me away.
不是的，史蒂芬
It's not true,
Stephen.
你妈妈和我经过长时间的商量...
Your mother and I had a long conversation...
- 商量什么？ - 我们需要缓一缓，史蒂芬！
- About what?  - We need a break, Stephen!
- 我不想缓一缓！ - 好吗？
- I don't want a break!  - All right?
- 我们两个，好吗？ - 闭嘴！我恨你！
- Both of us, okay?  - Shut up! I hate you!
- 冷静 冷静！ - 不，别碰我！
- Just calm down. Calm down!  - No, don't touch me!
- 别碰我！ - 你冷静！
- Don't touch me!  - You just calm down!
- 别碰我！ - 冷静！
- Don't touch me!  - Calm down!
禁 闭
六个月后
醒醒，醒醒
Wakey, wakey.
起床了
Rise and shine.
你准备好复健了吗？
You ready for your workout?
张开嘴
Open.
...很可能整个新英格兰地区的暴雪
...significant snowfall likely across all of New England
总之 就是这样
when all is said and done.
随着暴风雪的临近
So, as the storm approaches
你要确定 采取了必要的预防措施
you'll want to make sure you take the necessary precautions here
准备好 你所在的地区会有重大的降雪...
and plan on some very heavy snow in your area for much of...
轮到你了
It's your turn.
要不要试试看？
How about a quick try?
很棒
Great job.
嗨
Hey.
我想继续再给他治疗几周
So I'd like to continue working with him
继续治疗几周
for another couple weeks.
这不是我的决定
It's not my decision.
他们要送他去波士顿
They're moving him to Boston.
一个聋哑儿童的福利机构
Some group home for deaf kids.
但我们在进步
But we're making progress.
这些事 需要时间
These things take time.
他是个好孩子，我们可以...
He's a great kid,we can...
他上周又打断了一个孩子的胳膊
He broke another kid's arm last week.
他不能留在斯威策
He can't stay at Sweetser.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我们要走了
We're leaving.
琼！
Joan!
等一下
Wait a second.
我觉得 就像...
I guess it was like a...
我觉得 就像所有聪明人的证书
I guess it was like certificates for all the smart people
所以 基本上 我什么都没有
so basically I have nothing.
我... 我没有...
I... I did not...
我想送给你这个
I want you to have these.
别冻着，好吗？
Keep warm, okay?
你不可能照顾缅因州所有的孩子,玛莉
Well, you can't take care of every kid in Maine, Mary.
我知道
I know.
呃...
Um...
没有人会因为你需要帮助 而瞧不起你
No one would judge you for needing help.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨，威尔森医生
Hi, Dr. Wilson.
你怎么样？还好吗？
How are you? How's it all going?
漫长的一天
Long day.
漫长的一周
Long week.
史蒂芬一直让你分不开身，是不是？
Well, Stephen really keeps you on your toes, doesn't he?
他还好吗？
How's he doing?
我收到了文件
I received the papers.
我们要把他送到卡文顿
I'm moving him to Covington.
在身体上，我能照顾他
Physically, I can manage.
基本上没问题
Just about
但这不是他
but it's not him.
只是一个 我喂饭，擦洗，穿衣的一具肉体
It's just a body that I feed,and wash, and clothe.
在我失去理查德德的那一天 我也失去了他
I lost him that day I lost Richard in the car.
玛莉，身为心理医生 不等于就是好父母
Mary, being a psychologist doesn't make you a perfect parent.
没有这样的事
There's no such thing.
你做了 你认为是正确的事
You did what you thought was right.
我把他送走了
I sent him away.
我把我儿子送走了 现在他没了
I sent my son away and now he's gone.
妈妈会给你买一只模仿鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
如果这只模仿鸟不唱歌
And if that mockingbird don't sing
妈妈会给你
Mama's gonna buy you
买一个钻戒
A diamond ring
911，你有什么紧急情况？
911, what's your emergency?
喂？
Hello?
我是玛莉波特曼
Yes, this is Mary Portman
住在Delphi巷 28号
from 28 Delphi Lane.
我家里 好像有人进来了
I think there is an intruder in my house.
好，别挂电话
Okay, stay on the line.
波特曼夫人，妳在房子理吗？
Mrs. Portman,are you inside the house?
妳能听到我吗？
Can you hear me?
- 波特曼夫人，妳还在嘛？ - 喂？
- Mrs. Portman, are you still there?  - Hello?
对不起，我的错
I'm sorry, my mistake.
只是一只浣熊
It's just a raccoon.
给你 喝了能暖和
Here you go.This will warm you up.
你没事吧？
You okay?
噢 等等 喂？
Oh. Hold on. Hello?
琼，嗨 谢谢你回电话
Joan, hi.Thanks for calling back.
对不起 我知道 现在很晚了
I'm sorry,I know it's late.
你怎么到这里的？外面零下9度
How did he even get here? It's 15 degrees out.
我知道，但是 拜托，琼
I know it's not,but please, Joan.
我可以帮他
I can help him.
他可以住在这里
He could just stay here.
等一下 有这个必要吗？
Hang on a second.Is that necessary?
什么？让我... 给我个机会吧，好吗？
What? Let me... Give it a chance, okay?
我可以帮他
I can help him.
报警有什么用处？
What good could it do to involve the police?
我愿意承担这个风险 他才9岁，琼，拜托！
I'll take that chance. He's nine years old,for God's sake, Joan, please!
你能不能让他...
Can you just let him...
琼，我等一下再打给你
Joan, I'll call you back.
汤姆！
Tom!
天啊
Jesus.
汤姆！
Tom!
你回去之前 不在喝一杯吗，乔？
You sure I can't get you another before you head back out, Joe?
谢谢妳，玛莉 我要加快时间
Thanks, Mary.I'm gonna press on
开始挨家挨户打听
start going door to door.
这种低温 一个小孩子在外面不会活很久
A young kid out alone won't survive long in these temperatures.
...在他们的公司网站上
...though on their company website
削售额和转化率 要高得多
have much higher sales numbers and conversion rates.
我感觉很无助
I just feel so helpless.
是啊，我...
Yeah, I...
我一下午 都在外面找他
I've been out all afternoon looking for him myself.
噢，天啊，琼
Oh, God, Joan.
我不敢想象 他一个人在外面会是什么样子
I can't stand to think of him out there on his own.
好，呃...
Yeah, okay, um...
向我保证一有消息 就打电话给我
Well, just promise me you'll call as soon as you hear anything.
好
Okay.
好的
Great.
好 再见
Okay. Bye.
汤姆！
Tom!
玛莉？
Mary?
亲爱的？
Hon?
妳没听到我吗？我很担心
Didn't you hear me? I was worried.
妳在这里干什么？
What are you doing in here?
我，呃... 我刚才...
I, uh... I was just...
我想收拾一下史蒂芬的床万一...
I thought I'd make up Stephen's bed in case...
万一汤姆回来
In case Tom came back.
哦
Oh.
现在几点了？
What time is it?
很晚了
It's late.
亚伦哈特 正在办公室等妳
Aaron Hart is waiting for you in the office.
这孩子 一直都在不停的
I mean, the kid's been bouncing around foster homes
换领养家庭 那时 没人关心
for, like, half his life,but no one gave a shit then.
现在全镇的人
And now suddenly the whole town's
都突然开始关心了
decided it's time to give a shit.
妳知道 光是美国 每年就有
Do you know how many children run away
多少孩子 离家出走或失踪吗？
or go missing every year in the United States alone?
我不知道
I don't know.
妳看不出 这有多荒唐吗？
Don't you see how fucked up that is?
而且，这孩子死了 人人都知道
Besides, the kid's dead.Everyone knows it.
好的，亚伦，今天就谈到这里吧
Okay, Aaron, that's about all we have time for today.
随便，好的
Whatever, sure.
非常谢谢
Thanks a lot.
你爸爸要来接你吗？
Is your dad coming to get you?
嗯
Uh-huh.
青少年 啊？
Teenagers,huh?
怎么样？
How's it going?
他今天恨我更多
Does he hate me more or less
还是世界更多？
than he hates the rest of the world today?
没有，他只是不适应你们的搬家和离婚
No, he's just having a rough time with the move and the divorce.
有时候 我已经记不起 他几年前
Sometimes it's hard to remember he was just a cute little kid
还是个可爱的孩子喜欢和爸爸一起打棒球
who liked to throw a ball around with his dad a few years ago.
他现在一直很暴躁
He's so angry all the time.
会过去的
He'll get through it.
只是个尴尬的年龄
It's just a difficult age.
妳听说 暴风雪要来了吗？
You hear about this storm coming in?
是的
Yeah.
如果验变成冰爆
If it turns into an ice storm
可能会停电几天
we could be without power for at least a couple of days.
嗯
Mmm.
妳不能独自在这里
You probably shouldn't be up here all alone.
我和亚伦 打算去镇上的
Aaron and I are thinking of moving into
旅馆住几天 等风暴过去
one of the hotels in town to ride it out.
呃...
Uh...
如果我们一起去，也许我可以请你吃个晚饭
If we do, maybe I could take you for dinner.
我不会有事的 我们不会有事的
I'll be fine.We'll be fine.
我儿子生病了 我不能带他走动
My son, he's sick,so I can't really move him.
哦 我很遗憾
Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
我还不知道 妳有个儿子 他多大了？
I didn't even know you had a son.How old is he?
他18岁 史蒂芬 18岁
He's 18. Stephen's 18.
他是我的继子
He's my stepson.
我还不知道...
I didn't know that...
我丈夫过世了，所以
My husband passed away, actually
现在只有史蒂芬和我
so it's just Stephen and me now.
也许我们4个人 哪天可以一起吃个晚饭
Well, maybe the four of us can get dinner one day.
我们和两个暴躁的青少年
You know, you, me and our angry teenagers.
这不合适
Look, it's not really appropriate.
亚伦是我的病人，所以...
Aaron's my patient,so...
而且 他还在车上等你
And he's waiting for you in the car.
好的
Sure, okay.
呃，呃...
Uh, um...
听着，谢谢妳
Well, listen, thanks.
对不起，我...
Sorry, I just...
我希望 妳的儿子能好转
I hope your son feels better.
谢谢
Thanks.
天
Shit.
哦，该死
Oh, shit.
没事的
It's okay.
我感觉 我要疯了
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
玛莉，冷静
Mary, calm down.
听听妳说的话
Look, listen to what you're saying.
我当时在场 是真实的
I was there. It was real.
妳是个理性的成年人
You're a rational adult.
世上并没有鬼，妳是知道的
There's no such things as ghosts,and you know that.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
我觉得 妳经历的是深眠状态
I think that you experienced something known as parasomnia.
一种能引发夜惊的睡眠失调
A sleep disorder that can trigger night terrors.
但我... 看到了他 我看到了汤姆
I... But I saw him.I saw Tom.
人人都说他死了
Everybody's been saying he's dead
我一直希望这不是真的，但这确定是真的
and I kept wanting it not to be true, but it must be.
我觉得 考虑到妳受到的压力
I think that with the amount of stress you're under
以及妳已经有的睡眠失调
and the existence of disturbed sleep already
这完全说得通
it makes complete sense.
坦白说，妳知道
And frankly,you know, the fact that
妳看到出走的孩子 也能解释
you saw the runaway boy also tracks.
妳一直在找他
You know, you've been looking for him
妳担心他
you're worried about him.
这不意味着他死了，更不用说变成鬼纠缠妳
Does not mean he's dead,let alone haunting you.
妳觉得 妳梦里那个孩子的脚步声
Do you think that the sound of the child's footsteps
是不是因为妳想起
in your dream could be a reminder of the child that
妳失去的儿子？
you might think you've actually lost?
让你想起以前 妳儿子害怕时
You know, of the son that used to come into your room at night
就来妳房里
when he was scared.
妳觉得 妳梦里
Do you think that that voiceless child
那个不说话的孩子即可能是史蒂芬...
in your dream could be Stephen...
...也可能是汤姆？
...as much as it's Tom?
在车祸之前很长时间，我记得 妳就跟我说过
Long before the accident,I remember you telling me that
妳感觉 在失去史蒂芬
you were feeling like you were losing Stephen.
在失去妳的儿子
That you were losing your little boy.
妳还记得吗？
Do you remember that?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
我经历了很多不幸
I had been through so much.
是啊 跟我说说那个史蒂芬
Yeah. Well,tell me about that Stephen.
妳知道，车祸之前的史蒂芬
You know,Stephen before the accident.
甚至是他出现问题行为之前
Before the behavioral problems even.
有件事 我从没告诉你，那天早晨
I never told you this,but that morning
他求我 别把他送走
he begged me not to send him away.
继续
Go on.
史蒂芬一直怪在理查德德身上
Stephen always blamed Richard.
不过 是我找到了那所学校
But I was the one who found the school.
我不知道如何兼任他的心理医生和母亲
I just didn't know how to be his therapist and his mother.
玛莉？
Mary?
关于汤姆的噩梦
Look, the nightmare about Tom
可能是关于史蒂芬的
may be about Stephen
但是 这是因为一切都是关于史蒂芬
but that's because everything's about Stephen.
我想跟你谈谈 开点药
Look, I'd like to talk to you about prescribing something
来调和妳的睡眠，好吗？
to regulate your sleep, okay?
所以 我要做个血液检查
So I'm gonna need some blood work.
在此期间，妳照顾好自己
In the meantime,take care of yourself.
谢谢
Thanks.
...开始袭击人类
...starts to attack humans
即使我们不是它们的天然猎物
when we're not their natural prey.
科学家们 能找出办法防止这样的悲剧吗？
And can scientists find a way to prevent these tragic events?
嗨 对不起，我刚才 呃... 请进
Hi. Sorry, I was,uh... Come in.
这种鲨鱼是海洋中最非凡的鱼类
This shark is the most charismatic fish in the ocean.
大白鲨 体重可以超过4或5,000磅
White sharks can weigh in excess of 4 or 5,000 pounds.
体长超过20英呎 所以，这是一种很大的鱼
Get in excess of 20 feet long.So, that's a very big fish.
我们知道 这些鲨鱼可以活到...
We know that these sharks can live...
今天要为这位年轻人做什么？
So, what are we doing for this young man today, then?
不，是为我
Actually, it's for me.
我需要做个血液检查
I just need some blood work done.
妳生什么病了？
What's wrong with you?
没什么，我没事
Nothing, I'm fine.
那为什么 没去医生那里检查？
Then why haven't you taken yourself to the doctor?
我不想留下他一个人
I don't like to leave him alone.
我尽量少离开家
I try not to leave the house too much.
帅气的男孩
Handsome boy.
他的眼睛像妳
He's got your eyes.
他不...
He's not...
谢谢
Thank you.
妳自己一个人照顾他？
You take care of him on your own?
嗯
Mmm-hmm.
Hmm.
他看起来很好 强壮
He looks good.Strong.
妳一定照顾得很好
You must be doing something right.
妳这个年龄的女人血压不应该这么高
Blood pressure is too high for a woman your age.
我们能不能只是，呃...
Could we just, um...
是我多管闲事了
None of my beeswax.
我来
I get it.
妳等着就好
You just wait.
医生拿到血液检查结果之后也会这么对妳说的
The doctor will tell you the same thing when he gets the results.
妳什么时候送史蒂芬去？
So, when are you taking Stephen in?
月底
End of the month.
威尔森医生说我该开始练习离家了
Dr. Wilson says I need to start practicing leaving the nest.
这不算离家吧
I'm not really sure this counts.
我昨天在镇上 看到道格哈特了
I saw Doug Hart in town yesterday.
哦，天啊，我那天对他很不客气
Oh, my God,I was so rude to him.
有意思
Funny.
他还觉得 惹妳生气了
He thought he'd offended you.
妳该打电话给他
You should call him.
跟他约会
Ask him out.
也许 我只是打电话跟他道个歉
Maybe I should call him just to apologize.
是啊，道歉
Yeah, to apologize.
我那天 很不应该
I felt like such an ass the other day.
我不知情
I had no idea.
露西把情况都跟我说了
Lucy explained everything to me.
哦，她一定会的
Oh, of course she did.
妳一个人照顾他，一定很辛苦
That must have been hard,taking care of him by yourself.
这也是她跟你说的？
She told you about that, too?
是的，史蒂芬...
And yes, Stephen...
我要把他送到一个护理中心
I'm moving him to a care home.
哦，对不起，我不知道她没有告诉我这个
Oh, I'm sorry, I had no idea.She didn't tell me that.
我以为...
I thought...
对不起 我...
I'm sorry. I...
你知道，我... 我都不会说话了...
You know, I... This is hard. I haven't...
我很久没跟男人一起吃饭了
I haven't done this in a while.
车祸之前 你们很亲近？
Were you guys close before the accident?
非常亲近
Very.
我和理查德德结婚时 他五岁
He was five when Richard and I got married.
他对我 比对他爸爸更亲近
He was closer to me than his dad.
但后来 他到了青春期
But then he hit puberty
就像家里有了一个陌生人
and it was like I had a stranger in the house.
我家的亚伦也是
Yeah, Aaron, too.I'm just like
就像完全换了一个人
he's a completely different species.
亚伦是个好孩子
Aaron is a good kid.
他的老师 不这么认为
Well, his teachers disagree.
我上周去见了校长
I had a meeting with the principal last week.
黑斯廷斯校长？他很差劲！
Principal Hastings? He's the worst!
史蒂芬也在那里上过学
So, Stephen went there, too.
但后来被开除了
Until he was expelled.
不会吧！为什么？
No! What for?
嗯，是学校小题大作了
Mmm, the whole thing was totally blown out of proportion.
几个学生 在游泳池里打闹
There were some kids,and they were messing around in the pool.
他们可能只是戏弄史蒂芬
And I guess they were just teasing Stephen.
有一天 他报复了，但没伤到任何人
One day he retaliated,but no one got hurt.
他生母去世后，他经历了很多痛苦
After his mom died,he was dealing with a lot of grief.
等他进入青春期，他几乎不跟任何人说话
And by the time he was a teenager,he barely spoke to anyone
只除了我，后来就出了 你知道...
except me,and then it was, you know...
我感觉 亚伦跟任何人都说话 只除了我
I feel like Aaron talks to everyone but me.
对我 完全不理不睬
He just completely shuts me out.
嗯
Hmm.
我想 我就不打扰你们休息了
Well, I guess I should let you two get to bed.
不早了
It's getting late.
史蒂芬？
Stephen?
我说过了，一定发生了什么，不只是我的幻觉
I told you, something's going on,and it's not just in my head.
玛莉，深呼吸
Mary, take a deep breath
然后 想想妳说的话
and think about what you're saying.
请听我说
Please just listen to me.
我以为是一个梦，但不是
I thought it was a dream,but it wasn't.
我当时醒着...
I was awake and...
是深眠状态...
Well, sleep parasomnia...
不是什么他妈的深眠状态，好吗？
It's not fucking sleep parasomnia, okay?
拜托，你一定要相信我
Please, you have to believe me.
听听妳说的话 妳在谈鬼！
And listen to what you're saying.You're talking about ghosts!
这不是妳
This isn't you.
真是的，难道我不知道 这听起来 很荒唐吗？
For God's sake, don't you think I know how this sounds?
一定发生了什么事 我能证明
Something is happening.I can prove it.
史蒂芬的脸上有抓痕
Stephen, he has scratches on his face.
妳睡眠不足
You are sleep deprived.
头脑不清
You're confused.
妳想搞明白一切
You're struggling to make sense of everything
然后得出了一些荒谬的解释
and latching onto irrational explanations.
听着，也许是妳不小心 抓了他的脸
Look, maybe you scratched him yourself by accident.
什么？
What?
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
我不知道 哪个更糟
I don't know what's worse.
要嘛 这些都是真事，要嘛 是我疯了
Either this really is happening,or I'm losing my mind.
我经常听到
I keep hearing these weird noises
墙里和地板下 有奇怪的声音
in the walls and under the floor.
玛莉，我是来帮妳的
Mary, I am here to help.
听着，我会催促他们尽快完成妳的血液检查
Listen, I'm gonna rush the lab for your blood work,
然后 就可以给妳
and then I think we should get you
开一些抗忧郁药
straight onto an anti-depressant.
几小时后 我们在聊，好吗？
I'll talk to you in a few hours, okay?
好
Okay.
现在是实时新闻
Now, to some breaking news
关于儿童福利机构几天前报告的...
concerning the young deaf boy reported missing several days ago...
...失踪聋哑儿童
...by Social Services.
不到一小时前
Within the past hour
有人在佛罗里达州哈索恩的一个公园里
a boy fitting the description of 9-year-old Tom Patterson
看到了和9岁的汤姆帕特森特征相符的男孩
has been spotted in a park in Hawthorne, Florida.
接到一个当地居民的报警之后
Acting on a call from a local resident
哈索恩警方 正在这一地区进行大规模的搜索
Hawthorne police are now conducting a wide search of the area.
他们怀疑 他可能是乘长途汽车来这里
They speculate he may have traveled by Greyhound bus
但是 现在还不知道
but as yet are still to determine
他具体在哪里
his exact whereabouts.
接下来报导的是
We'll be back after the break with more
即将到来的暴风雪
on the winter storm heading our way.
- 只有我！ - 嗨！
- Only me!  - Hey!
我知道 妳说过 什么都不要，但是...
Okay, I know you said that you didn't need anything, but...
我也不是第一次了，露西
It's hardly my first rodeo, Luce.
呃…妳今晚真的不和我们一起吗？
Um... Sure you don't want to stay with us tonight?
不，我们没事
No, we're fine.
我刚才还以为...
For a moment there,I thought I was...
妳没事吧？
Are you okay?
是的，没什么
Yeah, it's nothing.
我只是一直没睡好
I just haven't been sleeping that well.
呃，妳真的什么都不缺了吗？
Um, sure you have everything?
灯笼？毛毯？
Lanterns? Blankets?
足够的木柴？
Enough wood?
是的，谢谢妳
Yes, thank you.
好吧，妳保重，好吗？
Okay, take care,all right?
好的，妳也是
Yeah, you, too.
好 再见
Yeah. Bye.
再见
Bye.
灯笼...
Lanterns...
- 哦，天啊...  - 是我
- Oh, God...  - It's just me.
你吓了我一跳
You scared me.
对不起 闯了进来 我敲过门，但没人应答
Sorry to barge in.I tried knocking, but no one answered.
我没听到你的车
I didn't hear your car.
有一辆铲雪车 挡住了你家的车道
Yeah, that plow just came.Your drive's blocked.
我只能把车停在路边走了过来
I had to park down the road and walk in.
哦 好的
Oh. Okay.
我来 是为了感谢妳昨晚的款待也来看看 妳还好吗
I just came to say thank you for last night and see if you're okay.
我和亚伦在假日饭店订了一间房间
Aaron and I did end up getting a suite down at the Holiday Inn
你们真的不和我们一起去吗？
so, you're sure you guys don't want to come with us?
不，你太客气了
No, that's kind of you.
我们经历过更坏的天气
We've weathered worse.
我昨晚很开心
I had a great time last night.
我也是
Me, too.
呃...
Um...
我真是无比的欣慰 他们找到了汤姆
I can't tell you what a relief it is they found Tom.
你知道，那个离家的孩子
You know,the runaway kid.
是啊，是啊，佛罗里达州
Yeah, yeah, Florida.
但后来发现 不是他
That turned out to be a false alarm.
妳没听说吗？
You didn't hear?
没有
No.
我相信他会出现的
I mean, I'm sure he's gonna turn up.
可能会在附近的某个镇上发现他
They'll probably find him two towns over.
...越向北 就越
...a little bit as you head further up to the north.
不管你怎么看
No matter how you look at it though
这都是一次严重的冬季风暴...
we're talking about a major winter storm...
妳不要紧吧？
You okay?
呃...
Uh...
我还有很多事要做
I have a lot to do.
我就不送你了
You don't mind letting yourself out.
好的
Sure.
道格！我...
Doug! I'm...
嗨，威尔森医生 抱歉，我刚才在楼下
Hi, Dr. Wilson.Sorry, I was downstairs.
- 玛莉？ - 是的
- Mary?  - Yeah.
我刚拿到了妳的血液检验报告
I have just gotten your blood work back from the lab.
好
Okay.
- 坦白说，我有些失望  - 什么？
- Frankly, I'm a little disappointed.  - What?
如果妳告诉我 妳在自行用药
If you'd have told me you were self-medicating
我们就能避免很多误会了
we could have avoided a lot of confusion here.
鉴于妳吃了那么多药
It's no wonder you're having so many problems
难怪妳出了那么多问题
given the amount of pills you're taking.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
玛莉，苯二氮平类药物不是随便能吃的
Mary, benzodiazepines are not a class of drugs we mess around with.
我什么都没吃
I'm not taking anything.
除了混合用药有可能会致命之外...
Aside from the fact that mixing prescription drugs can be lethal...
混合？
Mixing?
我只能估计 妳在吃史蒂芬的药
I can only assume that you are taking medication from Stephen
这不光威胁到妳的健康
which not only puts your health at risk
还有他的健康
but his also.
你没听我说 我不懂你说什么
You're not listening to me.I don't know what you're talking about.
我什么药都没吃
I haven't taken anything.
我本来 很愿意给你开一些有助于睡眠的药
I would have happily prescribed you something to help you sleep.
虽然药效会温和一些
It would have been less potent
但我确定会有效的
but of course I would have done it.
你搞错了，这不是我的血液检验结果
You've made a mistake,those are not my results.
对不起，我现在不方便说
I'm sorry, I really can't talk right now.
我回头再联系你
I'm gonna have to call you back.
玛莉
Mary.
玛莉！
Mary!
玛莉？玛莉？
Mary? Mary?
你拨打的电话
The number you are trying to call
无法接通
is not reachable.
史蒂芬 史蒂芬...
Stephen. Stephen...
不！住手！
No! Stop!
安静 小宝贝
Hush little baby
别说话
Don't say a word
妈妈会给你买一个模仿鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
如果这只模仿鸟
And if that mockingbird
妈妈会给你买一个...
Mama's gonna buy you a...
别怕 别怕 别怕 别怕 别怕
It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.It's okay. It's okay.
嘿 别怕 我在这里
Hey.It's okay. I'm here.
不，不，不，不，不，不！不！
No, no, no,no, no, no! No!
别怕 对不起 对不起
It's okay.I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
看着我 我是妳儿子，史蒂芬
Look. Look at me.It's your son, Stephen.
别怕 我要把它撕下来
It's okay.I'm gonna take this off.
好
Okay.
对不起 好吗
I'm sorry. Okay.
安静，不！嘘！
Hush, no! Shh!
别喊！
Don't scream!
没事 嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿
It's okay.Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
别怕
It's okay.
这是怎么一回事？拜托
What's happening? Please.
我在照顾妳
I'm taking care of you
就像妳照顾我
just like you take care of me.
我在做梦吗？
Am I dreaming?
不是
No.
不在是了
Not anymore.
我不明白
I don't understand.
这...
Is... And...
车祸一周后
When I woke up in the hospital
我在医院醒来
a week after the accident
妳在我身边
you were by my side
伺候我的一切
waiting on my every need.
但是你不动 你不说话
But you didn't move.You didn't speak.
是的
No.
你们都以为我不能
And you all assumed I couldn't.
我只是不希望这一切的结束
I just didn't want it to end.
我越是什么都不做，这事就越轻松
And the longer I did nothing,the easier it got.
医生一直对妳说
The doctors kept telling you
现在的医学对大脑的了解有多少
how little is known about the brain.
我那时不明白
I couldn't understand.
你的大脑扫描 一直在改善
Your scans kept improving.
你的反射也正常
Your reflexes were normal.
我只是看到了 你想看到的
You saw what you wanted to see.
这几个月，我们在一起 那么幸福
These last few months,we've been so happy together.
只有妳和我
Just you and me
直到他来了
until he came here.
汤姆
Tom.
我不能放他走
I couldn't let him go.
他看到我了
He'd seen me.
- 你杀了他  - 我是妳儿子！
- You killed him.  - I'm your son!
我是妳儿子
I'm your son.
妳为什么总是更关心他们？
Why did you always pick them over me?
我比不上他们吗
I won't compete anymore.
嘿，不，不 没事的 嘘
Hey, no, no.It's okay. Shh.
嘿，听着，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿
Hey, look, hey,hey, hey, hey.
没事的
It's okay.
他不是鬼
He's not a ghost.
他就在楼下
He's downstairs.
我本来打算杀了他，但是他爬进了管道间里
I was gonna deal with him,but he climbed into the crawlspace.
到我房间的 就是他
That was him in my room.
呃
Uh-huh.
我以为都过去了
Yeah, I thought it was all over.
但是我低估了这个药
But I underestimated these.
他还活着
He's alive.
我把他堵在里面
I blocked him in.
我等着他饿死
I was waiting for him to starve.
他的那个声音
That sound of him.
他在黑暗中刮擦的声音
That sound of him scratching around in the dark.
妳知道，在妳的茶里放一粒就能让妳安睡一整夜
You know, one in your tea used to put you down all night.
由于他来了之后我不得不加大了剂量
I had to up the dosage since he's been here.
嘿，过来，过来
Hey, come here,come here.
张开嘴
Open your mouth.
- 拜托  - 张开
- Please.  - Open.
不，不...
No, no...
啊！
Ow!
停下！停下！停下！
Stop it! Stop it!Stop it!
咽下去
Swallow.
乖女孩
Good girl.
等妳醒来时，他就不在了
When you wake up,he'll be gone.
我们就能回到正常
We can go back to normal.
只有妳和我 我保证
Just you and me.I promise.
喂？
Hello?
不！不，别再让我等
No! No,do not put me on hold again.
我需要你们派人去找玛莉波特曼
I need you to send someone out to see Mary Portman.
在Delphi巷 28号
At 28 Delphi Lane.
不 她...
No. She...
不，她没出事故
No, she has not been in an accident.
我觉得 她被下药了
I think she's being drugged.
妳已到达目的地
You have reached your destination.
什么？
What?
该死
Shit.
哦，天啊...
Oh, God...
闭嘴！
Shut up!
我以为妳会开心
I thought you'd be happy.
现在 妳不必把我送走了
Now you don't have to send me away.
我只想帮你，史蒂芬
I just want to help you, Stephen.
你出了严重的车祸
You were in a terrible accident.
你身体不好
You're not well.
我听见妳说了
I heard you
在昨晚
last night.
妳又要把我送走
You're trying to send me away again.
因为他！
Because of him!
不，不，不是因为他
No, no, it's not because of him.
妳把我的房间给了他
You gave him my room.
妳要替换我！
You're replacing me!
没人能取代你
No one could ever replace you.
我保证
I promise.
拜托，把斧头放下
Please, just put the ax down
我们可以谈谈
and we can talk bout this.
我能解决此事
I can fix this.
我们可以回到以前的样子
We can go back o how it was.
我还可以请人帮你，好吗？
And I can get you ome help, okay?
拜托，把斧头放下
Please, just put he ax down.
枪里没有子弹
It's not loaded.
我这是为了我们！
I'm doing this for us!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
我要带你离开这里
I'm gonna get you ut of here.
不！
No!
快跑！
Run!
史蒂芬，拜托，住手！
Stephen, please, stop!
别说了！别说了！妳要毁了一切
Stop it! Stop it! ou're ruining everything.
冷静
Calm down.
我是在帮妳收拾残局
I am trying to fix our mess.
史蒂芬，这不是你
Stephen,this isn't you.
闭嘴 快闭嘴 妳不了解我
Shut up. Just shut up.You don't know me.
- 你是一个好孩子 史蒂芬  - 不
- You're a good boy, Stephen.  - No.
只是因为车祸
It was just the accident.
那不是意外车祸！
It wasn't an accident!
我不在乎自己的死活 只要能撞死他
I didn't care if I died as long as he did.
妳是我的一切... 妳...
You're what I... You...
妳要把我送走
You were sending me away.
我必须阻止他
I had to stop him.
我不能让他带我离开妳
I couldn't let him take me away from you.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
我宁愿死 也不想离开妳
I would rather die than be away from you.
嘘...
Shh...
我们不需要别人
We don't need anyone else.
哦，天啊 汤姆！
Oh, God. Tom!
不！
No!
哦，天啊 你在哪里？
Oh, God. Where are you?
哦，汤姆
Oh, Tom.
汤姆，来
Tom, come.
下来 来
Come down. Come.
跟我来 快！
Come with me. Quick!
安静 小宝贝
Hush little baby
别说话
Don't say a word
妈妈会给你买一只模仿鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
如果这只模仿鸟不唱歌
And if that mockingbird won't sing
玛莉？
Mary?
我是威尔森医生，妳...
It's Dr. Wilson, are you...
妳没事吧？
Are you okay?
玛莉？
Mary?
有人在家吗？
Anybody home?
你们都好吧？
Everybody okay?
我觉得，呃
I just thought we'd, uh
在警察来之前 我们该聊一聊
have a little chat before the police get here.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
我觉得 我们没时间...
I don't really think that we have time for...
没时间玩游戏，是嘛？
For games right now, do we?
史蒂芬，我是威尔森医生
Stephen, it's Dr. Wilson.
史蒂芬？
Stephen?
你要她送走我
You told her to get rid of me.
但是 她爱我
But she loves me.
没人能分开我们
And no one is gonna keep us apart.
汤姆 没事，他走了
Tom. It's okay, he's gone.
没事
It's okay.
这里 穿上
Here. Put this on.
他来了
He's coming.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
你待在这里
You stay here.
我会回来找你的
I'm coming back for you.
哦，天啊，道格！
Oh, God, Doug!
快，跟我来
Quick, come with me.
等等...
Wait...
在这里等着 等等
Wait here. Wait.
威尔森医生...
Dr. Wilson...
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事的 我会带你离开这里
It's okay. I'm gonna
get you out of here.
他在这里...
He was here...
一直都在
The whole time.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
在史蒂芬的脑子里...
In Stephen's mind...
不要去反驳他的错觉
Don't challenge his delusions.
妳知道吗？
You understand?
别让他看到那个孩子
Don't let him see the boy.
他要的是妳，只有妳
It's you he wants, only you.
进入他的错觉中...
Enter his delusions...
没事的，我帮你
It's okay, I get you.
不 带那个孩子走
No. Get the boy out.
哦，天啊！
Oh, God!
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
待在这里
Stay here.
没事的
It's okay.
不！
No!
住手！住手！拜托！
Stop! Stop! Please!
不，住手！
No, stop it!
不，听我说
No, listen to me.
- 住手 听我说  - 不！不！
- Stop. Listen to me.  - No! No!
冷静，冷静
Calm down, calm down.
你说的对，好吗？
You were right, okay?
我专注于我的病人
I was focused on my patients
没能考虑到你
when I should have been thinking about you.
- 不！不，已经太晚了！ - 等等！住手！
- No! No, too late!  - Wait! Stop!
我不知道
I didn't know.
我不明白 你这么做 是为了我们
I didn't understand that you were doing it for us.
我不知道
I didn't know.
为了我们能在一起
So that we could be together.
不 妳撒谎！妳在帮他
No. You liar! You're helping him.
- 不，我赶走了他  - 不
- No, I got rid of him.  - No.
是的！他现在走了
I did! He's gone now.
现在只有你和我，我保证！
It's just you and me,I promise!
- 这是我们的房子  - 不
- This is our house.  - No.
你说的对
You were right.
他不该在这里
He shouldn't be here.
是我胡涂
I was confused.
我以为失去了你
I thought I'd lost you.
但现在 你在这里
But now you're here.
我怎么可能替换你？
How could I ever replace you?
我爱你，史蒂芬
I love you, Stephen.
这里就是你的归宿
This is where you belong.
妳！
You!
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
汤姆
Tom.
那里没有路 快！
There's no way down from there. Quick!
我接着妳
I got you.
好的
That's it.
好，我们走 我们走 快
Okay, let's go.Let's go. Quick.
我们走
Let's go.
汤姆！
Tom!
快跑，汤姆！
Run, Tom!
走！
Go!
史蒂芬，不！
Stephen, no!
拜托！
Please!
请不要
Please, no.
让开
Move.
不！
No!
汤姆！汤姆！
Tom! Tom!
我接着你 我接着你
I got you. I got you.
我接着...
I got...
妳准备好这么做了吗？
Are you ready to do this?
玛莉 是的
Yup, I am.
我和他都是
We both are.
我会为你们办好手续的
The papers will be waiting for you.
谢谢，琼
Thanks, Joan.
他是一个幸运的孩子
He's a lucky kid.
我能看看吗？
Can I see?
很好
It's good.
你想要一只狗？
You want a dog?
有可能
Maybe.
他会很好的
It's gonna be good.
如果这只模仿鸟不唱歌
And if that mockingbird don't sing
妈妈会给你买一个钻戒
Mama's gonna buy you a diamond ring
安静，小宝贝，别说话
Hush, little baby,don't say a word
妈妈会给你买一只模仿鸟
Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
谢谢观赏
浮水印